

# Asen Bochukov

● Online CV ● Linkedin ● Location: Sofia, Bulgaria ● Phone: +359899890459 ● email:bochukov.asen@gmail.com



Online CV
LinkedIn Profile

### **Certificates:**



Java8 Oracle
Programmer Certified
Associate



Decipher
Programming
Certification



Business Acumen
Training Series PwC
2015



Soft Skills Course 2015



Completed Course Of AutoCad Civil 3D I am Java 8 Oracle Certified Developer. I am reasonable and reliable person with responsible attitude to work and hunger to learn and grow professionally. During the entire term of my services to all previous organizations, my knowledge, working abilities and techniques have always won the appreciation of my managers.

I am working as a Java Software Engineer at Coherent Solutions.

In my current project I am using Spring Boot, Docker containers, Bamboo, GIT, Bitbucket, Oracle Database, Intellij, Maven, Scrum methodology and JIRA.

I have graduated from the <u>Technological School Electronic Systems</u> associated with Technical University of Sofia, from where I have a diploma for a specialist in electronic computing systems.

My vision is that playing as a team player is the only way to play.

# **Experience:**

04.2020-Present

Java Software Engineer at Coherent Solutions

Main activities and responsibilities

As a Java Software Engineer I am working with Spring Boot, Docker containers, Bamboo, GIT, Bitbucket, Oracle Database, Intellij, Maven, Scrum methodology and JIRA. . I have every day Scrum meeting with our US client.

### 11.2017-04.2020

Java Software Engineer II at Scale Focus

• Main activities and responsibilities

As a Java Software Engineer II I am working with Spring Boot, Docker containers, Jenkins, GIT, MongoDB, RabbitMQ, Intellij, Gradle, and JIRA. I have every day Scrum meeting with our US client so we are getting the active tasks aligned for the active sprint and backlog stories groomed for the future sprints.

## **Education:**

# ✓ Fresno State

Decipher Programming Certification

## ✓ Telerik Academy

Student Courses , C#, JavaScript HTML, CSS

✓ <u>Technical school</u> <u>electronic systems - Technical</u> University Sofia

Specialist electronic computing machines

✓ <u>University of</u>
Architecture, Civil Engineering and Geodesy

Engineer – surveyor master's degree

# **Key Skills:**

Always protecting the reputation and interest of the employer.

Working methodically and constantly to achieve the goals!

Experienced in working for International companies!

Experienced in management of a crew!

Sharing the fun with the team!

### 11.2015-12.2016

## Survey Programmer at Focus Vision

• Main activities and responsibilities

As a Survey Programmer, I am responsible for programming online surveys, working as part of a client centric team, delivering services to leading market research firms. My job responsibilities include programming and troubleshooting surveys to verify they function according to specifications and standards, following formalized quality assurance and project processes, and maintaining an exceptionally high level of quality for client deliverables. My position involves daily interaction and coordination with internal departments and requires excellent communication skills.

## 01.2015-08.2015

Student at <u>Telerik Academy</u>

• Main activities and responsibilities

I have been through several courses like C#, JavaScript, HTML and CSS.

My mission is to be better today than yesterday, each day!